Guide to the Records of the Associate Vice President for Academic Affairs, Leslie Berlowitz 1970-1980 RG 9.5
New York University Archives
- Series I: Topical Files
  - Trustee presentation--charts, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Goals Statement--Copies and galleys, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Goals Statement--Draft #4--original, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Goals Statement--Draft #4--working copy, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Goals Statement--Revised per Senate meeting--copy, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Goals Statement--Revised per Senate meeting--working copy, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Goals Statement--Deans' summary--originals, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Goals Statement--Deans' summary--copies, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Goals Statement--Deans' summary--working copy, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Goals Statement--Copy, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Goals Statement--Working copy, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Goals Statement--Copies, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Goals Statement--Working copy (including Bromberg's), 1975 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Goals Statement--Original, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Goals Statement--Copies, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Goals Statement--Working copy, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Goals Statement--Reaction to Aug. 11 draft, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Goals Statement--Draft original, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Goals Statement--Draft--working copy, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Goals Statement--Copy, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Goals Statement--Working copy, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence to President Hester, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Goals--Correspondence to Dr. Sawhill, undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence to Steering Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Goals--General file, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Goals--General file, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Goals--Marland memo, undated (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Meetings--JCS, WFP, LJO, LCT, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Meetings--JCS, LJO, LCT, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Meetings--Steering Committee, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Meetings--JCS, LJO, WFP, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Meetings--JCS, LJO, LCT, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Pending--JCS memos to University community/to Deans, undated (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Goals Statement--Rader drafts--originals, undated (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Goals Statement--Rader drafts--copies, undated (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Report of the Task Force on the NYU College of Dentistry, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226133 2
  - Untitled, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Goals for the Decade Ahead, 1974-1983, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Meeting--Dr. Hester, Oliva, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Materials for meeting, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Planning conference--President Hester's notes, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Sample topic--final draft, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Steering meeting #13, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Steering meeting #14, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Steering meeting #15, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Steering meeting #16, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Meeting with Dr. Hester, Payne, Oliva, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Steering meeting #17, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Steering meeting #18, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Steering meeting #19, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Untitled, undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Steering committee meeting, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - 2:00 meeting, undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Planning conference--instructions for physical arrangements, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Research--A Philosophy of NYU, undated (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Plans for the Decade Ahead, undated (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Plan for Action, undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Steering committee meetings--NYU goals study, undated (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Washington Square Daily News, undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Steering committee notes, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Report of Short-Range Goals--LCT and LJO, undated (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Planning meetings, undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Goals conference notes, undated (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence--goals study, undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Arthur Rubin instructions, undated (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Planning conference--Provisional agenda, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Conference attendance, undated (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Plans for the Decade Ahead, 1964-1973, undated (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Provisional calendar, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Faculty statistics, 1963-1973 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Student enrollment report, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Student enrollment report, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Goals conference mailing labels, undated (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Goals study--Advisory panel, undated (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Goals study--Original copies, undated (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Goals study--Reference copies, undated (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Goals study--Suggested December conference participants, undated (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - International education--Sally Guthrie, undated (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Memos to President Hester, undated (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - Memoranda to VP Payne, undated (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - Letters to Steering Committee--LCT, undated (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - NYU Goals--Statewide master plans, undated (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - LT's notes--Planning conference, undated (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Dean Tuttleton--Meeting with President Hester, undated (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Preliminary meetings, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - General notes--Planning sessions, undated (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - LEDD Planning Conference, undated (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Pre-conference notes--Proposed topics outline, undated (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - ACE freshman profile, undated (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Goals study--Follow-up letter, undated (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Goals study--Groups, undated (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Goals conference--Mailing lists, undated (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Goals study--Papers, undated (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Plans for goals conference, undated (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Reports--Leaders, co-leaders, topic reporters, undated (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Goals study--Requests for papers, undated (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Notes Steering committee meeting no. 1 9/28, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226134 0
  - Steering Committee meeting no. 2 10/8, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Steering Committee meeting no. 3 10/15, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Steering Committee meeting no. 4 10/18, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Steering Committee meeting no. 5 10/29, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Steering Committee meeting no. 6 11/12, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Steering Committee meeting no. 7, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Steering Committee meeting no. 8 1/14, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Steering Committee meeting no. 9 1/27, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Steering Committee meeting no.10 2/25, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Steering Committee meeting no. 11 3/4, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Steering Committee meeting no. 12 3/18, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Undergraduate curriculum project-extra copies of reports, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Undergraduate curriculum project-reports from other universities 8/76, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Study on undergraduate education articles on liberal arts etc., 1975-1977 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Articles - liberal arts and professional schools, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Study on undergraduate education articles on literacy, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Law School Writing Seminar - student evaluations, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Study on undergraduate education background UWW BA requirements, undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Study on undergraduate education background CAS BA requirements, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Study on undergraduate education background SSW BS requirements, undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Study on undergraduate education background SOA BFA requirements, undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Study on undergraduate education background SEHNAP BS requirements, undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Study on undergraduate education background SCG general studies program, undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Study on undergraduate education background BPA BS requirements, undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Undergraduate Curriculum project - final reports 3/1976 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Study on undergraduate education curriculum committees, lists, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Study on undergraduate education general correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Study on undergraduate education Honors College, undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Study on undergraduate education membership lists, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Study on undergraduate education William Paterson Conference, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Study on undergraduate education Regents Recommendations, undated (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Study on undergraduate education report 1/1976 draft (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Study Group Master List, undated (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Study on undergraduate education meeting no. 1 organizational committee 11/1976 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Study on undergraduate education meeting no. 2 organizational committee 11/1976 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Study on undergraduate education meeting no. 3 organizational committee 12/1976 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Study on undergraduate education meeting no. 4 2/1977 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Study on undergraduate education meeting no. 5 4/1977 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Organizational Committee Meeting with JCS May 20, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Organizational Committee LCT meeting notes (all meetings), 1976 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Study on undergraduate education proposed nominations study groups, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - GEC: Study Groups List, undated (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Study on undergraduate education LCT/working notes/study groups, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Study on undergraduate education study group leaders/meetings 3/1977 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - English Workshops Freshman Program, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - English Expression, 1976-1977 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Aethestic Experience, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Study a Foreign Language, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Natural and Biological Worlds, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Study Group on Science, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Ethics, Values and Moral Awareness, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Mathematical Competence, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Social Experience, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Civilization and Cultures, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Study in Undergraduate Education Study Groups - Addresses, undated (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Study in Undergraduate Education Study Groups - Room Assignments, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Study Groups Status Reports, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Study Groups Final Reports (originals), 1977 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Senate Meeting Dockets and Minutes, 1973-1977 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - General Education Conference-Publicity, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04226135 7
  - General Education Conference- Instructions/Booklet, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - General Education Conference- Directory of Participants, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - General Education Conference- Publicity, printing, supplies, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - General Education Conference- Letters of Invitations/Extras and Mailing Lists, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - General Education Conference- Workshop Lists, undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Study Group Reports- Draft Versions, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - General Education Conference- General Correspondence, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - General Education Conference- Siggested Topics for Discussion, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - General Education Conference- Poster, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - General Education Conference- Preparations/Rooms, etc., 1977 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - General Education Conference- Letters of Invitations/ Originals, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - General Education Conference- Group Leader Suggestions, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - General Education Conference- Registration Forms, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - General Education Conference- Registration Forms Returned, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - General Education Conference-Agenda, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Complete Set-Conference Materials, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Mathematical Competence, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - English Expression, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Aesthetic Experience, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Natural and Biological Worlds, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Understanding of Social Experience, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Civilizations and Cultures, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Ethics, Values and Moral Awareness, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - General Education Conference- Workshop Reports( originals), 1977 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Botstein Article, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Griffiths Report, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - General Education Conference--Topic Reporters, Notes, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - General Education Conference--Letters/Thank Yous, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Suggestions Generated By Conference, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Excerpt from Manuel Paper, undated (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - General Education Conference--Report to the Trustees, May 2, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Change Reprints, undated (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Extra Copies of Goals Papers: A-1, Meyers: Some Ideas to Improve the Financial Prospects for the University, Dec 1973 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04227200 8
  - A-2 Payne: What Are the Financial Prosepcts for New York University, Feb 1974 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - A-3, Burneson: Increasing Economies in University Operations from an Institutional View, Nov 1973 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - A-4, Goren: The Future Relationship of NYU to Other City and State Institutions, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - A-5, Roth: Organization for Research at New York University in the Coming University, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - A-7, ADMC: Ad Hc Committee on Preparation of AM Siegel's Statement, Nov 1973 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - A-8, deGrazia, Frayssinhes: Institutional Planning for NYU, Nov 1973 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - B-1, Hook, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - B-2. Ross: How to Make Use of the City's Resources to Enrich Curriculum, Student and Faculty Life, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - B-3, Leifer and Burdowski: The Environment for Students at NYU, undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - B-4, Maggin: The Environment for Faculty and Staff at NYU, undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - B-5, Kosak: Environment for Faculty at NYU, undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - B-6, Hester, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - B-7, Donahue, Frayssinhes, Huntington: The Character of the NYU Experience, undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - C-1, Kosak: The Future Role of Science at NYU, undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - C-2, Guth, undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - C-3, Raymo: The Future Role of the Humanities at New York University, undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - C-11, Clair, Deming, Frayssinhes: Academic Planning I-The Disciplines, undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - D-1, Farr: Graduate and Professional Education at New York University, undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - D-2, Oliva, undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - D-3, Tuttleton: A Proposal for an Nyu Instutute of the Humanities, undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - D-5, Smith: The Role of Continuing Edcation at New York University, undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - D-6, Smith: Proposed Changnes at NYU, undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - E-1, London: The Future of Innovative Programs at NYU, undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - E-2,Oppenheim: The fUture Uses of the Communications Media for the Advancement of NYU"s Educational Services, Dec 1973 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - E-3, Baker: More Effective Teaching and Learning at New York University, Nov 1973 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - E-4, Kennedy: The New York University Libraries, a Look to the Future 1974-1984, Nov 1973 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - E-5, Burns, Park: Alternate Media Center, undated (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - E-6, Boise, Frayssienhes, Weaver, Solanky: Academic Planning III-Techniques, undated (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - F-1, Goran: Whom DO We Educate Locally and What Areas Should Be Developed to Be of Greater Service and Attraction to This Constituency, undated (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - F-2, Livesey: Whom Do We Educate Nationally and What Areas Should Be Developed to Be of Greater Service and Attraction to This Constituency, Nov 1973 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - F-3, Konigsberg: The Future Role of Summer Session Education at NYU, Nov 1973 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - F-4, Adkins: Higher Education and the Changing Job Market for Degree Holders, Jan 1974 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - F-5, Brown: What Is the Role of NYU In Relation to the Disadvantaged Segment of the Urban population, undated (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - F-6, Rosen, Stewart: The Roots of Social and Academic Malpractice Toward the Urban Disadvantaged, Nov 1973 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - F-7, Smith: The Mission of the School of Continuing Education, Nov 1973 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - F-8, Guthrie, Hull: The Constituencies We Serve, Nov 1973 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Report on Planning for the Future of the School of Education, undated (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Report of Fiscal Review Group, May 19051976 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Goals Statement Originals, Sep 1975 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04227201 6
  - Goals Conference NYU Report, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Summary Sheets Preliminary Reports Goal Study, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Reports: Miscellaneous, 19731974 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Untitled (Goals Conference), 1974 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Dean Tuttleton, Nov 1973-Dec 1973 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Untitled (Goals Conference and Institutional Planning), Mar 1974 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Steering Committee Working Papers, 1973-1974 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - LC Tuttleton Co-Leader Reports, Mar 1974 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Goals Study Additional Copies, May 26, 1905-1974 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04227202 4
  - Registration Forms, Faculty and Administration, NYU Conference on Goals for the Next Decade, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Letters from the President RE: Goals Study, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Goals Conference, Feb 1974-Mar 1974 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Goals Conference-Reservations, Nov 1973 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Registration Forms, Alumni, NYU Conference on Goals for the Next Decade, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Registration Forms Returned, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Registration Forms, Staff, NYU Conference on Goals for the Next Decade, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Registration Forms, Students, NYU Conference on Goals for the Next Decade, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Dr. Hester, Reports of Topic Groups, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Contact Cards, undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Background, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04227203 2
  - "Knowledge and Power in Medicine" JCS Medical Alumni Day Speech, May 1978 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - NEH Proposal to Strengthen the Humanistic Proposal at NYU, 1976-1978 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Nexus, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Communications Degree Programs for Mrs. Tuttleton's Review, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Foreign Student Project, Sep 1974 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Foreign Student Questionnaire Responses, Sep 1974 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - A Guide to Health Related Professions, Proofs, Jul 1977 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Proofs, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Internship Booklet, Corrections for Second Printing, Oct 1977 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Internship Booklet, Mar 1977-Jul 1977 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Communications Booklet, Retyped, undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Health Related Booklet, Reactions, Oct 1977 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Health Program Guide, Persons Recieveing Copies, Oct 1977 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Miscellaneous, Health Related, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Health Professions Booklet, Preliminary Copy, Edited Draft, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Health Booklet, Working Copy, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Health Related Professions, Corrections for Second Printing, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Health Studies Booklet: Preliminary Research Materials, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Health Studies Booklet: Health Interview Notes, undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Health Studies Booklet: Hand-Written Drafts, undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Health Studies Booklet: Typed Drafts, undated (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Health Related Professions Booklet: First Completed Draft, Jun 1976 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Health Professions Booklet, Edited Version of Draft Number One, Nov 1976 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Advanced Study Final Copy, Jul 1975 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Advanced Study, Final Copy Original, undated (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Advanced Study, Working Copies, May 1975-Jul 1975 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Advanced Study Notes of Meeting, Admissions Brochure, Mar 1975 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Health Related Professions Booklet, Background Material, 1973-1975 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Booklets, Master Copy and Proofs of Advanced Study Booklet, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Combined Degree Booklet, Fall Correspondence, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04227204 0
  - Combined Degree Booklet, Vol II, Working Copies, Jun 1975 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Combined Degree Booklet, Vol II, Final Copy, May 1976 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Combined Degree Prgram Booklets, Proofs, Jul 1975 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Booklet Series General File, Jun 1975-Oct 1975 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Booklets-General, Miscellaneous, Notes, etc., 1975-1976 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Booklets Series--Costs, Jun 1975-Jul 1975 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Booklets, JCS Letter to the Class of 1979, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Booklets, JCS Letter to the Class of 1976, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Booklets, JCS Letter to the Class of 1977, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Booklets, JCS Letter to the Class of 1978, undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Booklets, JCS Letter to the Class of 1980, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Sawhill: Letter to the Class of 1978 and 1981, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Booklets-Posters, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Combined Degree, Vol I, Final Copy/Originals, undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Combined Degree, Vol I, Coordinators Comments/Revisions, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Combined Degree, Vol I, Working Copies, undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Combined Degree, Working Papers, Prelims, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Booklets, Editorial Miscellaneous, undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Combined Degree Booklets, Second Edition Final Galley, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Combined Degree Booklet, Vol I, Revised, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - General Education Conference-Report/Draft versions, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    Barcode #: 3 1142 04227205 7
  - Ethics Study Group: Final Report, undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Math Study Report Follow-up, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Study Group on English Final Report, Oct 1977 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Final Report: Study Groups on Aesthetic and Moral Experience, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Final Report: Social Order Study Group, undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Science Study Group: Final Report, Mar 1978 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Organizational Group-Meeting (Moral Awareness), Dec 1978 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Organizational Group Meeting, Aug 1978 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - English Study Group: Materials For Meeting, undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Study Group on Civilization and Culture:Final Report, undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Follow-up Culture and Civilization Final Report, Feb 1978 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - English Study Group Conference Reports, Apr 1977 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Conference on Public Awareness, Oct 1977 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Cost of English Writing Program, Feb 1978 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Follow-up English Report: Curriculum Committee Materials, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Expository Writing Program, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Organizational Group Meeting: Notes, Mar 1978 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Statewide Conference, Jun 1977-Jul 1977 (Box 14, Folder 19)